<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" ?> 												
<artifacts>												
  <project_id>1</project_id> 												
  <artifact_type>Trial Implementations Dataset Complete</artifact_type> 												
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN1	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Process Laboratory Order: Laboratory creates the test results and sends the results to the data repository for availability to the ordering clinician and other providers of care, if appropriate.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN2	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Verify integrity of test result (file) contents and that the results came from the identified source.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN3	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Authorize release of laboratory test results: Test results released to clinician based on verification as ordering clinician or provider of care status and other appropriate restrictions for use.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN4	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Process Request for Laboratory Test Results: The data repository receives a request for test result content and verifies the authenticity of the clinician, the integrity of the request, and any restrictions for use.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN5	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The test results should contain appropriate patient information and other information per agreed to standards and policies.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN6	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Providers of care should be known.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN7	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Where new results cannot be unequivocally matched with a patient, an exception list should be produced to allow human resolution	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN8	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	View results using another clinical data system (non-EHR system): Not all clinicians will initially have an EHR to view lab test results. The clinician may view lab test results using a clinical data system (non-EHR).	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN9	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Send request for lab test result content to data repository(ies): The clinician selects data repository(ies) from which to retrieve lab test results and sends a request(s). The request is sent via a web application, or other clinical data system.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN10	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Lab results are viewed through a web application or other clinical data system.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN11	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Print lab results	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN12	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Save lab results in local system for viewing at a later time: This action assumes that no EHR system is available. The clinician may wish to save lab results to the local system to review at a later time. This is distinct from importing the data into the EHR.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN13	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Verify correct patient identity and correctness of lab results and error correct if necessary: Upon review of the result, a clinician may see suspect data (e.g. that should be confidential, or may be erroneous). Error correction communication is a manual process.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN14	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Acknowledge receipt of lab results: Upon receipt of the lab result the clinical data system sends an acknowledgement to the NHIE.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN15	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Log interaction with data repository	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN16	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Send acknowledgment to laboratory that integrity, authenticity and completeness of results are found.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN17	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Store test lab results	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN18	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Store lab results in data repository system and note any restrictions for use (e.g., providers of care list, patient consent restrictions, or sensitivity restrictions).	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN19	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Transmit lab test results to ordering clinician and other providers of care if appropriate	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN20	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Log receipt and storage of lab test results	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN21	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Authenticate to locator service	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN22	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Create test results	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN23	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Send result location and related information to locator service. This should contain appropriate patient information and other information per agreed to standards and policies. Restrictions for use should also be provided by data repository (from laboratory) if not provided through supporting community or regional services.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN24	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Log interaction with locator system	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN25	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	methods to identify and authenticate users.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN26	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	methods to identify and determine providers of care.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN27	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	methods to enforce data access authorization policies.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN28	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	methods to ensure the veracity of data,	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN29	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	methods to correctly match patients across systems.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN30	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Clinicians have registered with the HIE and consumer access consents have been established	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN31	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Clinicians securely access lab test results either through an EHR system (local or remote) or a clinical data system.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN32	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Security and privacy policies, procedures and practices are commonly implemented to support acceptable levels of patient privacy and security.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN33	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Send results to data repository	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN34	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Appropriate standards protocols; patient identification methodology; consent; privacy and security procedures; coding, vocabulary and normalization standards have been agreed to by all relevant participants.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN35	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Legal and governance policies regarding data access authorizations, data ownership, and data use are in effect.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN36	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Secure electronic transport and consent as defined by the HITSP security and privacy constructs is assumed between sender(s) and receiver(s)	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN37	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The data repository receives a request for test result content and verifies the authenticity of the clinician, the integrity of the request, and any restrictions for use. 	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN38	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The data repository either sends the test results for integration into the clinician’s EHR, or sends the content to another clinical data system for viewing. 	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN39	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The secrecy of the content is maintained during transmission.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN40	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Receive and validate the query request	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN41	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Parse, validate, and acknowledge received data query requests.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN42	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Authenticate and verify as ordering clinician or provider of care: May include provider identification and validation of credentials, privileges and/or other authorization.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN43	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The laboratory transmits the results to the data repository with appropriate metadata necessary for indexing and browse/query response.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN44	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Authentication and verification may be provided through community or regional services. This may include a trust relationship whereby the clinician is authenticated and authorized once by the community or regional service.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN45	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The authentication and verification is then carried through the query/retrieval processes.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN46	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Test results released to clinician based on verification as ordering clinician or provider of care status and other appropriate restrictions for use.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN47	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Transmit lab results of an identified patient to an ordering clinician or provider of care	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN48	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The means of transport will vary depending on whether an EHR system is available to receive the results, or if a web application is used.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN49	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Receive lab test result as ordering clinician or provider of care: New test results, upon completion, may be sent directly to the clinician’s EHR system (local or remote) without an intermediate request action.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN50	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Send request for historical lab test result content to data repository(ies): The clinician selects data repository(ies) from which to retrieve lab test results and sends a request(s). The request may be sent from the EHR system or via web application.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN51	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Submit authentication information to the data repository	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN52	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Confirm data integrity of received results: Upon receiving the test result set (messages), the EHR system confirms that the message was received in a complete and unchanged format.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN53	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The data repository may be within the laboratory, may be a separate entity, or may be part of a community or regional service provider	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN54	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Parse and validate results content: The EHR system opens and parses each electronic result. Individual records are checked for appropriate information, completeness, proper codes, and patient identifying information.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN55	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Merge data into EHR: The EHR aggregates patient data from each data repository. Each received record is processed and correlated to a patient in the EHR system. Where new results cannot be unequivocally matched with a patient, an exception list should be produced to allow human resolution	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN56	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	New results are flagged within EHR: The EHR system should provide a clear indicator as to the status the review process of all results by clinicians	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN57	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Acknowledge receipt of lab results: A message is sent to the lab data repository indicating which results were successfully processed and indicates any results that were undeliverable and unprocessed.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN58	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Log receipt of lab test results: Include patient consent information in log.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN59	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Produce exception list of errors: Where inbound lab results records cannot be unequivocally matched with the EHR, an exception list is produced to allow human resolution	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN60	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Query for laboratory (historical) test results: The clinician queries the locator service for the availability and location of lab test results for a specified patient and receives the location of the results.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN61	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Queries to the locator service could be accomplished either through the EHR user interface directly or through another clinical data system.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN62	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Submit authentication: Establish clinician’s identity and verify whether clinician is a provider of care	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN63	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Receive test results from laboratory.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN64	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	One of many authentication methods could be used (biometrics, card, token or user ID and password, cryptographic techniques).	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN65	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Clinician and locator system agree on patient identity through patient trait matching	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN66	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The clinician and locator system must verify that they are interacting about the same patient.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN67	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Patient identity may be agreed upon by a number of means including demographic information, agreed-to mapping of patient IDs, or shared patient ID.The means is dependent on whether the locator service is provided by a third-party, or part of available community or regional services. 	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN68	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	A set of traits (such as name, DOB, gender, etc.) may be used by a locator service to perform a probabilistic match. 	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN69	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Business rules could be established across a community or region to determine minimum acceptable combinations of traits (for example, name-only searches not allowed without a DOB). 	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN70	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Provides the functionality for a priori agreed to identifiers by the clinician and locator service and lab data repository.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN71	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Clinician and locator system agree on patient identity based on shared MPI: If the entity to which the clinician is affiliated (hospital, HMO, private physician practice, etc.) has already registered the patient internally and uploaded the entry into a shared MPI, the provider can capture and submit the entity's internal identifier for that patient (e.g., the patient's medical record number for that hospital) to a locator service. 	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>	In this case, the provider would not need to manually enter demographic traits (name, date of birth [DOB], etc.) since that data are already present in the MPI.	</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN72	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Clinician and locator system agree on patient identity based on patient identifier matching	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN73	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The locator system matches the patient identifiers supplied by the clinician with patient identifiers known within the locator service.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN74	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The laboratory test results as well as any pertinent information necessary for indexing and browse/query should be provided.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN75	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Transmit request for specific lab test results based on order number or other unique test result identification: The clinician may request specific test results based on a unique identification number, eliminating the need for browsing through all available test results. This can be performed through a web application or through a standards-based query request from the clinician’s EHR.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN76	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Browse, select and confirm the relevant test results for the correct patient and transmit request	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN77	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Based on the patient information provided by the clinician (either the entity identifier or demographic traits), a list of candidate patient matches will be retrieved from the locator service. This list should contain demographic data that will help the clinician determine which of the potential matches actually corresponds to the patient. ...	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>	From the list of candidates previously retrieved, the clinician will select and confirm the entry or entries that correspond to the patient and those applicable to reason for query (e.g. date range, test groups, etc.). The clinician may also determine that none of the candidates in the list are correct matches.	</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN78	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Receive the data repository location where the test results are stored: The locator service provides pointer (i.e., links) to the location(s) where the test result(s) are stored. The clinician uses these locations to retrieve the test results.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN79	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Log interaction with locator service	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN80	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Clinician should have proper identification/authorization to access patient-specific information everywhere such information exists;	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN81	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Clinician should be able to uniquely identify patient for which information has been requested;	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN82	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Clinician request will return ALL information available for the specific patient; and	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN83	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Proper action should be taken when results updates are sent for error correction, completeness, etc.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN84	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Record locator service should have lab data locations for the specific patient.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN85	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Locations of lab results should be known to record locator service;	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN86	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Clinician should be able to retrieve more than 1 record at a time.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN87	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Clinician should have proper identification/authorization to access and review patient-specific information	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN88	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Authenticate clinician requesting laboratory test results	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN89	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Establish clinician’s identity and verify status as ordering clinician or provider of care. 	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN90	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Note that the clinician may be an individual, an organization or “system.” The nature of the identification/authentication will be different in each case.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN91	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The clinician and locator system must verify that they are interacting about the same patient. Patient identity may be agreed upon by a number means including demographic information, agreed-to mapping of patient IDs, or shared patient ID. The means is dependent on whether the locator service is provided by a third-party, or part of available community or regional services. A set of traits (such as name, DOB, gender, etc.) may be used by a locator service to perform a probabilistic match. ...	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>	Business rules could be established across a community or region to determine minimum acceptable combinations of traits (for example, name-only searches not allowed without a DOB).	</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN92	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Verify authenticity of laboratory and lab test result file contents	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN93	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Receive request for lab test results based on lab order number or other unique lab test identifier: The clinician may request specific test results based on a unique identification number, eliminating the need for browsing through all available test results. This can be performed through a web application or through a standards-based query request from the clinician’s EHR.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN94	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Provide lab result availability information based on clinician query/browse	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN95	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Authorize data release: Test result information released to clinician based on verification as ordering clinician or provider of care status and other appropriate restrictions for use.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN96	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Send lab result location (links) pointers to authorized clinician: The location pointers will be used by the clinician to retrieve the lab test results for either viewing or integration into the EHR.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN97	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Log interaction with clinician	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN98	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Queries to the locator service could be accomplished either through the EHR user interface directly or through another clinical data system.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN99	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Submit authentication information to locator system: Establish clinician’s identity and verify whether clinician is a provider of care Note that the clinician may be an individual, an organization or “system”.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	NHIN100	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The clinician may request specific test results based on a unique identification number, eliminating the need for browsing through all available test results. This can be performed through a web application or through a standards-based query request from the clinician’s EHR.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
</artifacts>												
