<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" ?> 												
<artifacts>												
  <project_id>1</project_id> 												
  <artifact_type>Consultations Dataset Complete</artifact_type> 												
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC1	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	In order for consumers to accept electronic health records, appropriate privacy and security protections may be needed to manage access to personal health information.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC2	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Consumers may also want to decide who will view and communicate their personal health information.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC3	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Privacy and security controls and the means of restricting data access are not standardized or regulated.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC4	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Without permissions and controls, consumer participation in the act of electronic health information exchange may be limited.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC5	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Without consistent standards, the viewing, accessing, or transmitting of electronic health information may be inhibited.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC6	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Incomplete, inaccurate, or proprietarily-formatted information prevents efficient health information exchange activities or utilization of electronic health information.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC7	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Without data standards that promote compatibility and interoperability, longitudinal patient medical records may be incomplete or of questionable integrity.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC8	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The processes identified in the use cases rely upon successful integration of EHRs into clinical activities. Because this integration may not align with current workflow and may require additional upfront costs, it may not be widely pursued or implemented.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC9	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Low adoption of HIT, particularly within rural areas and long-term care settings, may create disparate service levels and may adversely affect healthcare for these populations.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC10	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	In order to coordinate transfer of care, patient information is sent to a facility or provider to determine its ability to accept the patient. If a setting determines that it is not able to accept, the patient data may still be accessed by this setting.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC11	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Patient information within a setting may be updated after an initial information transfer of core data to the next provider of care has taken place.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC12	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Updated information may need to be communicated to providers and other stakeholders.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC13	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The patient is routinely evaluated by the clinician who documents each encounter in an EHR.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC14	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	During the normal course of care, the clinician may have ordered tests, received results, and prescribed medications.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC15	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The clinician may have access to additional patient information which could be gathered electronically via the patient’s personally controlled heath records which may include PHRs, health record banks, etc., or health information exchange, or from other provider EHRs and other sources that hold information about the patient.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC16	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The clinician evaluates the patient and reviews any relevant results received for previously ordered tests.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC17	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The clinician determines a need to send the patient to a clinician outside of the clinician’s institution for a consultation.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC18	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The clinician may seek another clinician’s opinion as a specialist or expert in a particular care area or as a second opinion.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC19	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The clinician discusses the need and reason for consultation with the patient.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC20	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The clinician may provide the patient with the name(s) of recommended clinicians, clinician practice, or facility.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC21	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The clinician may also assist the patient in selecting a particular clinician based upon the patient’s insurance coverage network and/or preferences.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC22	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The clinician recommends or selects a consulting clinician or is notified of the patient’s preference for the consulting clinician.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC23	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The clinician compiles and documents the relevant information for the request for consulting clinician electronically.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC24	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The request for consultation and core set of data is communicated electronically to the consulting clinician’s EHR	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC25	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The core set of data may provide the consulting clinician with reason for the consultation request, background on related treatment provided, request for a specific outcome (evaluation, validate with a second opinion, conduct a specific test or procedure, etc.).	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC26	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	A core dataset including (but not limited to) patient clinical data, medication reconciliation information, patient history, insurance information, and contact information for the requesting clinician is communicated to the consulting clinician electronically.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC27	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Additional information regarding datasets is provided in Section 10.0, which may be representative of the information contained within consult letter.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC28	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	If required, the requesting clinician may also include items needed for payor approval of the consultation such as an authorization number, referral valid end date, and/or authorization signature.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC29	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	There are standardization needs for the set of information clinicians may require to effectively understand the reason for requesting a consultation and communicating the relevant data for the consultation.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC30	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The clinician sends any additional relevant patient information or documentation to the consulting clinician that may not be included in the core set of data included in the consultation request.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC31	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Patient information may include (but is not limited to) copies of reports, images, EKG strips, etc. and could include any relevant information that is included within a patient’s medical record.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC32	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The clinician may receive an inquiry from the consulting clinician for additional patient data that was not included in the prior transmission of data.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC33	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Patient information may include (but is not limited to) historical patient documentation and test results.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC34	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The requesting clinician compiles patient information and provides access to the consulting clinician.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC35	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Patient information may include (but is not limited to) historical patient documentation and test results.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC36	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The requesting clinician receives the consult report electronically and accesses the information in the EHR.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC37	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The requesting clinician updates relevant patient information in the EHR to reflect the new treatment plan or continuation of current treatment plan based upon the consulting clinician’s recommendation.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC38	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The requesting clinician continues to evaluate and manage the patient and documents patient encounters in the EHR.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC39	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The consulting clinician receives a request for consultation and patient information electronically.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC40	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The clinician reviews the core set of patient information and consultation needs from the requesting clinician, assesses the urgency, and determines ability to accept the patient.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC41	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	If applicable, the request for consultation includes the necessary referral information (e.g., referring clinician information, referral date, number of visits, referral expiration date, and referral number) needed for insurance coverage for the consultation.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC42	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The consulting clinician may review patient data, evaluate the patient, and perform medication reconciliation for any modified medications as stated in the 2007 Medication Management Use Case.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC43	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Upon reviewing patient information and evaluating the patient, the consulting clinician may determine that a payor authorization is required for a service or equipment to be provided during the course of care for the patient and perform this electronically.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC44	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Authorization may be required for patient coverage for a procedure, test, or medical equipment (e.g. surgical, continuous glucose monitor, insulin pump, prosthetics).	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC45	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The requesting clinician may also have performed the necessary payor authorization as part of the referral process.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC46	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The consulting clinician may request additional patient data that was not included as part of the core set of consult data sent by the requesting clinician or as part of the request for consultation.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC47	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The consulting clinician receives and reviews additional patient data information electronically within the EHR from the requesting clinician or health information exchange.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC48	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Additional patient data information may include (but is not limited to) historical patient documentation such as prior hospital discharge summaries, historical results, imaging studies, etc.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC49	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Information received may be from the requesting clinician or from care received from other providers or facilities.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC50	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The consulting clinician provides care for the patient and documents patient encounter(s) in the EHR.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC51	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Consulting clinician completes consultation and documents patient encounter(s) in the EHR.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC52	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	After the consultation is completed, the patient may continue to be managed by the requesting or other clinicians.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC53	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The clinician completes the consultation and documents the summary of care provided in the form of a consult report.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC54	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	It may be possible that the consultation request may need to be processed as a referral and the consulting clinician may continue to provide care for or manage the patient.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC55	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	A consultation report is communicated to the requesting clinician and may include: summary of treatment provided, recommended continued treatment plan, and medication reconciliation information (medications stopped, medications changed, added, or put on hold and a complete current medication list per the 2007 Medication Management Detailed Use Case).	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC56	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	This consult report is communicated to the requesting clinician, patient, and any other related providers of care.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC57	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The requesting clinician may provide the patient with the name(s) of recommended clinicians or assist the patient in selecting a particular clinician based upon the patient’s insurance coverage network and/or preferences.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC58	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The patient may self-initiate a consultation when seeking a second opinion or direct consultation.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC59	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The patient schedules an office visit with the consulting clinician.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC60	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The patient may create and/or update their list of providers and determine the access permissions that should be granted to those providers for their personally controlled health information as described in the Consumer Empowerment: 2007 Consumer Access to Clinical Information Detailed Use Case.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC61	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The patient may also grant privileges to a consulting clinician to access personal health data within a health record bank.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC62	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	In a self-initiated consultation, the patient may provide permission to existing providers of care to share the core set of data associated with a consultation request.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC63	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The patient is evaluated by the consulting clinician and receives care/treatment as directed.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC64	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The patient may be instructed to stop, modify, or take new medications during the course of treatment.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC65	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	During the course of treatment, the patient may access updated clinical information via health information exchange as described in the Consumer Empowerment: 2007 Consumer Access to Clinical Information Detailed Use Case.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC66	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The patient is able to access a copy of the consult report sent to the requesting clinician in the personally controlled heath records which may include PHRs, health record banks, etc.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC67	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The patient may continue to receive care from the requesting clinician upon completion of the consultation or continue to receive care from the consulting clinician or other providers.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC68	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	For a self-initiated consult, the patient may select a clinician for follow-up care or continue receiving care from the consulting clinician.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC69	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The patient is routinely evaluated by the clinician who documents each encounter in an EHR.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC70	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Depending on the care setting, there may be a variety of care providers and health support personnel that provide care for the patient and document in the EHR.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC71	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Care coordinators (such as Clinical Nurse Specialists, Home Health Nurses, Physical Therapists, Social Workers, Case Managers, Nurse Practitioners, and Discharge Planners in the hospital setting) may begin planning for discharge and transfer throughout the patient’s episode of care.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC72	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The care coordinator identifies the environment from which the patient originated (home, nursing home, etc.) and considers whether the patient may require transfer to another care setting (e.g., rehabilitation, assisted living, home health) upon discharge.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC73	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Upon notification that the patient is ready to be transferred to another care setting, the care coordinator may consult other care providers to obtain input for preparing for the transfer to another care setting and review documentation from other care providers within the EHR.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC74	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The clinician determines the next setting of care.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC75	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The care coordinator may select potential options and locations for the patient and review them with the patient and/or family.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC76	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The patient/family may provide feedback to the care coordinator regarding preferred facilities or home health agencies.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC77	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Communication with the patient’s payor and determination of authorization and/or coverage for transfer may be included in the coordination activities of the discharging care setting.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC78	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Authorization may be required for coverage approval to patient transfer to the next care setting.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC79	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The care coordinator has been notified of the preferred option(s) for transfer and prepares for the transfer coordination process.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC80	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The clinician and care coordinators begin the discharge documentation process which includes information such as transfer coordination and plan of care information.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC81	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The care coordinator begins the transfer coordination process by communicating electronically the core set of data needed to determine whether the receiving setting can accept the patient.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC82	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	It is important for the receiving setting to have critical information that determines the ability of the receiving setting to accept the patient based upon special patient care needs such as the presence of lines and catheters, oxygen requirements, cognitive status, and skin conditions/pressure ulcers.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC83	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Insurance details and power of attorney information is also needed during this coordination process.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC84	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The type of data that is needed by the receiving setting includes (but is not limited to): patient demographic information, insurance/administrative information, reason for admission and history of present illness, expected date of transfer, transfer instructions, problems, medications, allergies, past medical history, treatment summary, advance directives, case manager/discharge planning notes, functional status, plan of care/discharge orders, pertinent labs, and pending tests.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC85	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Upon reviewing patient data received, the receiving is able to accept the patient and notifies the discharging/transferring as such.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC86	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The receiving care setting notifies the discharging/transferring setting that it is unable to accept the patient.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC87	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The discharging/transferring setting conducts the transfer coordination process with another facility/setting.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC88	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The clinician continues the discharge planning process. This may include development of discharge orders/care plan, discharge summary, and review of pending tests.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC89	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The patient is discharged and transferred to the next setting of care. Relevant patient information is communicated to the transport team as appropriate.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC90	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The core set of transfer data that is available at time of discharge is communicated to the receiving setting.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC91	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	This information is also utilized by the transport team that may be transporting the patient to the next care setting.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC92	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The core set of transfer data is communicated to the patient’s personally controlled heath records which may include PHRs, health record banks, etc. and the other care providers for the patient such as the primary care physician.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC93	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	In addition to the core transfer dataset, additional relevant patient information may be communicated to the receiving care setting. This may include documentation such as images, EKGs, case manager documentation, therapies (PT/OT/ST) documentation, history and physical, nursing notes, operative notes, etc.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC94	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The core dataset may be the same set of data that was communicated during the transfer coordination process, but the comprehensive information may not be completed at time of transfer coordination or at the time of actual patient discharge/transfer.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC95	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The discharge summary may be not completed and all pending tests may not be resulted at the time of actual patient discharge and may need to be communicated when available.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC96	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Core patient data such as the discharge summary or pending test results may become available after the patient has been discharged.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC97	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Patient data may be modified or annotated after patient discharge.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC98	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Newly available data that is part of the core set of transfer data is communicated to the receiving setting. This information is also communicated to the patient and other transfer dataset recipients such as the primary care physician and patient.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC99	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The receiving care setting and other transfer dataset recipients may receive annotated data that is part of the core transfer dataset or a may receive a notification that annotated data is available on a patient.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC100	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Patient information is reviewed by the clinician at the receiving care setting.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC101	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	At any time during the course of care for the patient in the receiving setting, a clinician may request additional data from the discharging/transferring setting.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC102	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The receiving setting is provided access to the additional patient data requested.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC103	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The types of additional information needs are broad and vary based upon patient details. This information could be in electronic and/or paper format.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC104	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The care coordinator or clinician at the receiving setting receives a request to accept a patient. This request includes information that is critical to determining whether the receiving setting is able to accept the patient.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC105	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Information received in the EHR includes (but is not limited to) the presence of lines and catheters, oxygen requirements, cognitive status, and skin conditions/pressure ulcers.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC106	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Insurance details and power of attorney information is also needed or communicated during this coordination process.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC107	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	There are standardization needs to develop the core data set to coordinate a transfer of a patient. The type of data that is needed by the receiving setting includes (but is not limited to): patient demographic information, insurance/administrative information, reason for admission and history of present illness, expected date of transfer, transfer instructions, problems, medications, allergies, past medical history, treatment summary, advance directives, ...	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>	case manager/discharge planning notes, functional status, plan of care/discharge orders, pertinent labs, and pending tests.	</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC108	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The receiving setting determines the ability to accept the patient based upon patient care information received.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC109	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	If needed, the receiving setting may request additional data from the discharging/transferring setting to make this determination.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC110	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The receiving setting notifies the discharging/transferring setting that it is able to accept the patient and continues the process of transfer coordination.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC111	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The receiving setting determines it does not have the ability to accept the patient based upon patient care information received or current census.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC112	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	If needed, the receiving setting may request additional data from the discharging/transferring setting to make this determination.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC113	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The receiving setting notifies the discharging/transferring setting that it is unable to accept the patient.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC114	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The receiving setting completes any preparations required for the patient’s arrival and addresses any special care and equipment needs based upon information received in the core transfer dataset.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC115	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The core transfer dataset and additional relevant patient information (images, EKGs, case manager documentation, therapies (PT/OT/ST) documentation, history and physical, nursing notes, operative notes, etc.) is received from the discharging/transferring setting.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC116	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The core dataset may be the same set of data that was communicated during the transfer coordination process, but the comprehensive information may not be completed at time of transfer coordination or at the time of actual patient discharge/transfer.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC117	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The discharge summary may be not completed and all pending tests may not be resulted at the time of actual patient discharge and may be received after patient arrival to the receiving care setting.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC118	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The receiving setting continues and completes any preparations required for the patient’s arrival and addresses any special care and equipment needs based upon information received in the core transfer data sent at time of discharge from the transferring setting.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC119	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The clinician at the receiving setting reviews patient data received from the discharging/ transferring setting.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC120	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Upon patient arrival, the transport team verbally communicates relevant information to the receiving setting and may provide documentation of information captured during transport.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC121	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The clinician at the receiving setting evaluates the patient upon arrival.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC122	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The clinician initiates admission orders, performs reconciliation of medications during this process, and enacts a care plan for the patient within an EHR.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC123	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	When the patient is ready to be discharged or transferred to another setting, the receiving care setting now becomes the discharging/transferring setting and follows the processes outlined within that setting.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC124	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The clinician receives and reviews data that is part of the core set of transfer data that was pending at time of patient transfer (e.g., discharge summary, pending tests).	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC125	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	If any data previously received was modified, the receiving care setting may receive modified or annotated data, or may receive notification that updated information may be accessed.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC126	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	If required, the clinician makes any modifications to the patient’s care plan as appropriate.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC127	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The receiving care setting continues to provide care for the patient and document patient information within an EHR.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC128	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	When the patient is ready to be discharged or transferred to another setting, the receiving care setting now becomes the discharging/transferring setting and follows the processes outlined within that setting.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC129	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The receiving setting requests additional information from the discharging/transferring setting or other available data sources via health information exchange.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC130	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Access additional patient data via health information exchange in the EHR.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC131	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The receiving care setting continues to provide care for the patient and document patient information within an EHR.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC132	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	When the patient is ready to be discharged or transferred to another setting, the receiving care setting now becomes the discharging/transferring setting and follows the processes outlined within that setting.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC133	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Discharge/transfer information is communicated to the patient’s personally controlled heath record which may include PHRs, health record banks, etc., via health information exchange for access by the patient and/or family members.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC134	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	The patient may receive newly available data generated after discharge or data that may have been modified or annotated after discharge.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC135	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Data delivery – including secure data delivery, data receipt and confirmation of delivery to EHRs, personally controlled health records, other systems and networks. Capability to securely deliver data to the intended recipient, confirm delivery, including the ability to route data based on message content, if required. For example, the request for consultation is delivered to the consulting clinician along with relevant clinical information.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC136	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Data retrieval – including data lookup, retrieval and data location registries. Capability to locate and retrieve requested data subject to consumer access decisions and local policies. For example, after evaluating the request for consultation, the consulting clinician may need to review additional clinical information about patient.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC137	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Subject-data matching. Capability to match available data to the appropriate person during retrieval or routing. For example, when the consulting clinician requests additional clinical information for a specific person, the systems, processes and policies facilitating information exchange are utilized to confirm that the data available for retrieval match the person of interest to the clinician.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC138	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Summary patient record exchange. Capability to exchange a summary patient record including, at times, the capability to compose the summary record from available data. …	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>	For example, information provided during a consultation or transfer in care would include core consultation data or core transfer data, respectively, which is delivered to the receiving patient care organization or location. In addition to core data, additional relevant patient information for the consultation/transfer may be exchanged.	</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC139	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Support for notification of availability of new/updated data. Capability to inform recipients that new or updated information is available for subsequent review or retrieval. For example, in a transfer in care situation, additional relevant clinical information may become available after a summary patient record has already been communicated (pathology report, discharge summary, etc.)	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC140	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Support for personally controlled health records – including managing consumer-identified locations to store their personally controlled health information; support consumer requests for information as well as routing of information to the consumer’s preferred personally controlled health record. Capability to maintain and implement information identifying the consumers preferred personally controlled health record (e.g., a PHR or health record bank) to support data routing and retrieval. 	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>	For example, a consultation report provided by the clinician could be delivered to the consumer’s preferred personally controlled health record through this process. Similarly, a consumer could retrieve and retain a consultation summary in their personally controlled health record.	</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC141	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	Emergency access – including capabilities to support appropriate individual and population emergency access needs. Capability to enable access to health information in extra-ordinary situations during which an individual may need emergency care but due to their health status is incapable of granting access permissions, or in the case of a public health emergency during which the health status of a population needs to be determined.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>	For example, this need could arise if an individual who has elected to not participate in network exchange of their information subsequently experiences a health situation which requires emergency care while they are incapacitated or unconscious.	</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC142	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	In emergency situations, public health officials may need to access an individual’s health information in order to identify populations or specific individuals at-risk.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC143	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	data integrity and non-repudiation checking.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC144	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	subject and user identity arbitration with like identities during information exchanges.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC145	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	access logging and error handling for data access and exchange.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC146	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	consumer review of disclosure and access logs	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
  <artifact>	  <art_id>	CToC147	</art_id> 	  <art_title>	routing consumer requests to correct data.	</art_title> 	  <art_parent /> 	  <art_content>		</art_content> 	  <art_type /> 	  </artifact>
</artifacts>												
