<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<artifacts_collection>
  <collection_info>
    <id>grp17_low_level</id>
    <name>Waterloo grp17_low_level</name>
    <version>1.1</version>
    <description>Waterloo grp17_low_level</description>
  </collection_info>
  <artifacts>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC1</id>
      <content>Event: Administrator manages system hardware through the system console
System: Server
Actors: Administrator
Overview: This use case captures how an Administrator manages the hardware of the system.</content>
      <parent_id />
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC2</id>
      <content>Event: Administrator attempt to logon/off to the server
System: Server
Actors: Administrator
Overview: This use case captures the process of the administrator logging on/off the server.
User ID and password are passed as inputs.</content>
      <parent_id />
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC3</id>
      <content>Event: Administrator making changes to the user account settings
System: Server
Actors: Administrator
Overview: This use case captures the process of the administrator making changes to the user account information</content>
      <parent_id />
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC4</id>
      <content>Event: Hardware test running automatically (every 30 secs)
System: Server
Actors: Timer
Overview: This use case captures the process of a hardware test running automatically</content>
      <parent_id />
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC5</id>
      <content>Event: Administrator making changes to bill plan information
System: Server
Actors: Administrator
Overview: This use case captures the process of the administrator making changes to the billing plan</content>
      <parent_id />
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC6</id>
      <content>Event: Administrator make changes to the IP-Phone mapping
System: Server, Phone Subsystem`
Actors: Administrator, Caller
Overview: This use case captures the process of the administrator making changes to the IP-Phone mapping</content>
      <parent_id />
    </artifact>
    <artifact>
      <id>UC7</id>
      <content>Event: Caller picks up the phone and dials a number to place a call to callee
System: Server, Phone Subsystem
Actors: Caller, Callee
Overview: Captures the process of a complete calling sequence from caller picks up the phone to either party hangs up.</content>
      <parent_id />
    </artifact>
  </artifacts>
</artifacts_collection>